

OKORO CHIMEZIE BRIGHT

Full-Stack Web Developer

PROFILE

I'm a full-stack web developer with over 4 years' experience in software development.

Experienced in meeting clients to collect software requirements, leading teams, excellent communication skills with problem solving skills, supporting engineers and software architecture.

Agile or water-fall development practice with html5, css3, JavaScript and cross-browser compatibility.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+841252181203 or 0394755263

WFBSITF:

https://okorochimezieportfolio1.netlify.app/

GITHUB:

https://github.com/mezieb

FMAII:

Okorobright13@gmail.com

CURRENT LOCATION: Hanoi, Vietnam.

HOBBIES

- Reading
- Listening to music
- Swimming
- Meeting people

EDUCATION

University of Nigeria Nuskka, UNN.

2007 - 2011

Mathematics (B.Sc./Ed).

FPT University, Hanoi, Vietnam.

2015 - 2017

Software Engineering (M, SE). Area of specialization data analytic.

Industrial training courses.

Udemy certification 2021

Course: The Complete 2021 Web Development Bootcamp.

Instructors: Dr Angela Yu.

Certificate no: UC-72bd0c3a-79c0-487d-99fa-c64d1b8efc26

WORK EXPERIENCE

IGHOLINK SYSTEMS TECHOLOGIES NIGERIA Data Analyst

2011-2014

ROLE: 1: data collection

2: data analyzation

3: research

Cong ty co phan ANTI-Antti GROUP VIETNAM Sales rep

2016-2019

ROLE: 1: research

2: data analyst

3: meeting clients

4: sales rep

5: team leader

Freelancer Web Developer

2019-till date

Client: spago Vietnam

Project type: spa management tools
Project link: https://www.spago.vn/

Role: frontend developer

I help you design your ideal website from simple to complex, with a business solution that suit your business needs in phases.

Feel free to contact me and let's do it together.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

1: HTML5

2: CSS3

3: JAVASCRIPT

4: REACT JS

5: BOOTSTRAP

6: GITHUB

7:PYTHON

8:FRAMEWORK - DJANGO

9:DATABASES - POSTGRESS, MYSQL